Oh my god, Sher...
我的天   雪莉
You are... you are insane.
你真是   你真是疯了
Um... I'm gonna go call the police.
啊   我要去报警
And tell them what?
你准备怎么跟他们解释呢
That you are a co conspirator in your husband's death?
说你是致你丈夫身亡的同谋
You remember your talk at lunch?
记得你在午饭时说的吗
How we discussed killing our husbands.
我们谈如何杀死我们的丈夫吗
It all worked out just fine for you, didn't it?
其实最后还是你受益   不是吗
You now own the entire ad agency
你现在拥有整个广告代理业务
and pretty soon you will be getting a large insurance policy check.
很快还会拿到一大笔的保险赔付
I don't think you will be calling the police any time soon, Kath...
你不会马上报警的   凯西
How'd you...? How could you do that?
你怎么能   你怎么下得了手
We were just talking.
我们只是在闲聊而已
I wasn't serious, it was just...talk.
我不是认真的   那只是闲聊
How did I know you didn't mean it?
我怎么知道你不是认真的呢